const ChemicalBondsQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What type of bond forms between two nonmetal atoms by sharing electrons?",
        options: ["Covalent bond", "Ionic bond", "Metallic bond"],
        correct_option: "Covalent bond"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the bond formed between a metal and a nonmetal by transferring electrons?",
        options: ["Ionic bond", "Covalent bond", "Hydrogen bond"],
        correct_option: "Ionic bond"
    },
    {
        question: "What type of bond is characterized by the attraction between oppositely charged ions?",
        options: ["Ionic bond", "Covalent bond", "Metallic bond"],
        correct_option: "Ionic bond"
    },
    {
        question: "In a covalent bond, how are electrons shared between atoms?",
        options: ["Equally", "Unequally", "Not shared"],
        correct_option: "Equally"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the term for a bond formed by the attraction between a hydrogen atom with a partial positive charge and an atom with a partial negative charge?",
        options: ["Hydrogen bond", "Covalent bond", "Ionic bond"],
        correct_option: "Hydrogen bond"
    },
    {
        question: "What type of bond occurs between atoms of the same element with similar electronegativities?",
        options: ["Nonpolar covalent bond", "Polar covalent bond", "Ionic bond"],
        correct_option: "Nonpolar covalent bond"
    },
    {
        question: "Which bond is strongest?",
        options: ["Covalent bond", "Ionic bond", "Metallic bond"],
        correct_option: "Covalent bond"
    },
    {
        question: "What type of bond is formed between atoms of different elements with different electronegativities?",
        options: ["Polar covalent bond", "Nonpolar covalent bond", "Ionic bond"],
        correct_option: "Polar covalent bond"
    },
    {
        question: "What type of bond occurs in metals?",
        options: ["Metallic bond", "Ionic bond", "Covalent bond"],
        correct_option: "Metallic bond"
    },
    {
        question: "What type of bond is formed when two atoms share electrons unevenly?",
        options: ["Polar covalent bond", "Nonpolar covalent bond", "Ionic bond"],
        correct_option: "Polar covalent bond"
    }
];

export default ChemicalBondsQuestions;
